Guide to the Peter S. Craig Papers, 1904-1983 MS2066
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Clippings, 1911-1980; Series 4; 10 Linear Feet
  - Clippings, 1971 September; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 1971 October; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Clippings, 1971 November; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Clippings, 1971 December; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1972 January; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1972 February; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 1972 March; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1972 April; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 1972 May; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1972 June; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 1)
  - Clippings, 1972 July; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 2)
  - Clippings, 1972 August; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 3)
  - Clippings, 1972 September; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 4)
  - Clippings, 1972 October; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 5)
  - Clippings, 1972 November; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 6)
  - Clippings, 1972 December; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 7)
  - Clippings, 1973 January; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 8)
  - Clippings, 1973 February; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 9)
  - Clippings, 1973 March; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 10)
  - Clippings, 1973 April; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 11)
  - Clippings, 1973 May; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 12)
  - Clippings, 1973 June; Series 4 (Box 59, Binder 13)
  - Clippings, 1973 July; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1973 August; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1973 September; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1973 October; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1973 November; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1973 December; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1971-1973; Series 4 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1974 January; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1974 February; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1974 March; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1974 April; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1974 May; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1974 June; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1975 January; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1975 May-July; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1975 August-December; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1976 January-June; Series 4 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1976 July-December; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1975-1980; Series 4 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, establishment of NCPPC, 1926; Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, George Washington Memorial Parkway, 1930-1933; Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Three Sisters Bridge, 1961-1967; Series 4 (Box 34, Binder 3)
  - American Civic Association, 1911-1926; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Appointments, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Area planning -- general, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Area planning -- general, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Area planning -- general, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Area zoning and buildings, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Bridges, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Civic groups (Home Rule), 1965; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Civic groups and leaders, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Congress -- committees, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Congress -- committees, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - DC area transit, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - DC budget and taxes, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - DC budget and taxes, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - DC budget and taxes, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - DC highways and bridges, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - DC -- roads and bridges, 1965; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - District -- federal planning, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - District -- federal planning, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - District -- federal planning, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Downtown redevelopment, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Downtown, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Downtown, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Downtown, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Editorials, Washington Star, 1959-1962; Series 4 (Box 34, Binder 1)
  - Editorials, Washington Star, 1962; Series 4 (Box 34, Binder 2)
  - Federal-aid highway program, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Federal transit policy, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Georgetown Palisades, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Georgetown Palisades, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Government appointments, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Government appointments, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Government appointments, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Government officials, 1965; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Government officials, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Legislative history of Capper-Cramton Act, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Mall and Foggy Bottom, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Mall and Foggy Bottom, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - National Capital Transportation Agency (rapid transit), 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - National Capital Transportation Agency (rapid transit), 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Northeast, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Northwest, 1966; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Northwest (west of Rock Creek), 1965; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Parks, trees, and monuments, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Parks, trees, and monuments, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Parks, trees, and monuments, 1963; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Parks, trees, and monuments, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Parks, trees, and monuments, 1965; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Planning and historical materials -- clippings, 1915-1916; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Planning and historical materials -- clippings, 1913-1926; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Planning and historical materials -- clippings, 1923; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Planning and historical materials -- clippings, 1926; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Planning and historical materials -- clippings, 1923-1939; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Rapid transit -- Legislation, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Roads -- DC, 1961; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Roads -- DC, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Roads -- Virginia, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Southwest Renewal Area, 1962; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Von Ackardt, 1964; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Index cards, 1923-1963; Series 5; 1 Linear Feet
  This series contains two boxes of index cards that summarize road and infrastructure projects in Washington, D.C. from 1923 to 1963. The cards appear to be arranged alphabetically by street address within the following geographic categories: F-SW, F-SE, F-NE, F-NW, NW, NC, NE, and Anacostia. It is clear that NW, SW, NE, etc. refer to the quadrants of the city, but it is not clear what F or NC stand for.
  Arranged alphabetically by street address within the following geographic categories: F-SW, F-SE, F-NE, F-NW, NW, NC, NE, and Anacostia.
  - Index cards of road and infrastructure projects: alphabetical within the categories NW, NC, F-NW, NE, and Anacostia, 1928-1962; Series 5 (Box 4, Carton 1)
  - Index cards of road and infrastructure projects: alphabetical within the categories F-SW, F-SE, F-NE, and F-NW, 1930-1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Carton 2)